I ignore yes slide very important
role in our life technology has changed the
face of education technology has changed
my life in different ways student is
hot and aware of interaction between 2
student and teacher with the help of
technology and also thing the definition of formal
education I have app website channel
block application also help in teachers
aujla district chairman made channels which
provide different type of information to
meaning
that all should make our life mode is shoddharthi
hr class 8 our comfortable
placed in online classes and student
can take admission in a course in any school
and unani schools colleges and
universities all around the world ayurveda
india and in akhrot dh also clarified
butter dal de dene labs
ko increase senior physician c of
plastic technology has strangers mode
of education in order to help in making a
teaching kajal meaning learning more a good
morning good night fall short improved
graphics nfc of law in india has to go a
long way to spread this benefit of
technology student can also celebrate
with their friends through technical application
and also I have option to the mode on
that no dear students of different way of
learning through which they get their due knowledge with the
positive and
that technology and just use to play the
point traditional five interesting videos
through online classes
128 also make our country chawla were also
connected to adab classmates started
online classes and truth and informed may
conditioner also all have connected to our
school and college through online class 8th
increase it also help to continue with
avarta sari online classes with the
teachers all aid patients with the
students
100 helps to several times all aid 2012 don't have to travel and
Tup Tup and Aavat difficult to our
online classes first ladies to
technology which help
hai pyar me demerits of technology
army camp directly sitting in front of
media was from this cream make awesome health
related to also helps in
98100 help the student to change his
ideal as well as his way of this
technology
hain ab maine hath all songs all drawbacks
of lies with increasing virtual
communication and also increase the social
phobia students in the 9th with this of
a mental give u who
is the best